export const bank = [
    {
        question: "What does “www” stand for in a website browser?",
        answer: "worldwideweb"
    },
    {
        question: "Which country do cities of Perth, Adelade & Brisbane belong to?",
        answer: "australia"
    },
    {
        question: "What geometric shape is generally used for stop signs?",
        answer: "octagon"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the biggest technology company in South Korea?",
        answer: "samsung"
    },
    {
        question: "Who was the first woman to win a Nobel Prize (in 1903)?",
        answer: "mariecurie"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the World's largest ocean?",
        answer: "pacific"
    },
    {
        question: "Who was the first woman pilot to fly solo across the Atlantic?",
        answer: "ameliaearhart"
    },
    {
        question: "Which country consumes the most chocolate per capita?",
        answer: "switzerland"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the most consumed manufactured drink in the world?",
        answer: "tea"
    },
    {
        question: "Which is the only edible food that never goes bad?",
        answer: "honey"
    },
    {
        question: "Which country invented ice cream?",
        answer: "china"
    },
    {
        question: "What was the first toy to be advertised on television?",
        answer: "potatohead"
    },
    {
        question: "What was the first feature-length animated movie ever released?",
        answer: "snowwhite"
    },
    {
        question: "Which Disney Princess talks to the most animals?",
        answer: "snowwhite"
    },
    {
        question: "Which member of the Beatles married Yoko Ono?",
        answer: "johnlennon"
    },
    {
        question: "What year was the very first model of the iPhone released?",
        answer: "2007"
    },
    {
        question: "What does “HTTP” stand for?",
        answer: "hypertexttransferprotocall"
    },
    {
        question: "What was Twitter’s original name?",
        answer: "twttr"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Blackpink debut song?",
        answer: "boombayah"
    },
    {
        question: "When did TWICE debut?",
        answer: "2015"
    },
    {
        question: "When did Blackpink debut?",
        answer: "2016"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the symbol for potassium?",
        answer: "k"
    },
    {
        question: "Which entry in the pokedex is Bulbasaur?",
        answer: "1"
    },
    {
        question: "Which planet is the hottest in the solar system?",
        answer: "venus"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of Batman’s butler?",
        answer: "alfred"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the first Pokemon in the pokedex?",
        answer: "bulbasaur"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the final evolution of bulbasaur?",
        answer: "venasaur"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the second evolution of bulbasaur?",
        answer: "ivysaur"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Bulbasaurs primary type?",
        answer: "grass"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the Pokemon Generation II grass starter?",
        answer: "chikorita"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Yoshi?",
        answer: "dinosaur"
    },
    {
        question: "What type of Pokemon is Pikachu?",
        answer: "electric"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is Sonic’s sidekick?",
        answer: "tails"
    },
    {
        question: "What was the original name of Mario?",
        answer: "jumpman"
    },
    {
        question: "What’s the most expensive video game ever produced?",
        answer: "starcitizen"
    },
    {
        question: "Zurich is the capital of?",
        answer: "switzerland"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Thailand’s capital city?",
        answer: "bangkok"
    },
    {
        question: "What country does the Rhine River run through?",
        answer: "germany"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the driest continent on Earth?",
        answer: "antartica"
    },
    {
        question: "What country formerly ruled Iceland?",
        answer: "denmark"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the lowest point of the US?",
        answer: "deathvalley"
    },
    {
        question: "What place is known as the largest micro-continent?",
        answer: "madagascar"
    },
    {
        question: "What country ends with the letter Q?",
        answer: "iraq"
    },
    {
        question: "What city hosted the 2014 Winter Olympics?",
        answer: "sochi"
    }
]
